{
	"articles":
	[
		{
		"id": 1,
		"questions": 
		[
			  {
				"ID": 1,
				"Question": "Where was the term “Artificial Intelligence” born?",
				"AnswerOne": "At the MIT",
				"AnswerTwo": "At the Dartmouth Conference",
				"AnswerThree": "At the Yale University",
				"AnswerFour": "At the ITEC Conference",
				"RightAnswer": "At the Dartmouth Conference"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 2,
				"Question": "What was the first industrial robot?",
				"AnswerOne": "Eliza",
				"AnswerTwo": "Deep Blue",
				"AnswerThree": "Shakey",
				"AnswerFour": "Unimate",
				"RightAnswer": "Unimate"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 3,
				"Question": "Which company developed AIBO?",
				"AnswerOne": "Microsoft",
				"AnswerTwo": "Sony",
				"AnswerThree": "Apple",
				"AnswerFour": "Samsung",
				"RightAnswer": "Sony"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 4,
				"Question": "How many chess matches has Deep Blue won against Garry Kasparov?",
				"AnswerOne": "1",
				"AnswerTwo": "0",
				"AnswerThree": "2",
				"AnswerFour": "3",
				"RightAnswer": "1"
			  }
			  
		]
		},
		{
		"id": 2,
		"questions": 
		[
			  {
				"ID": 1,
				"Question": "What is Roomba?",
				"AnswerOne": "A Chessbot",
				"AnswerTwo": "A question answering computer",
				"AnswerThree": "A vacuum cleaner",
				"AnswerFour": "A chatbot",
				"RightAnswer": "A vacuum cleaner"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 2,
				"Question": "On which operating system does Siri run?",
				"AnswerOne": "Windows",
				"AnswerTwo": "Android",
				"AnswerThree": "Linux",
				"AnswerFour": "IOS",
				"RightAnswer": "IOS"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 3,
				"Question": "What is the Product name of Alexa?",
				"AnswerOne": "Amazon Beta",
				"AnswerTwo": "Amazon Echo",
				"AnswerThree": "Amazon Eco",
				"AnswerFour": "Amazon Alpha",
				"RightAnswer": "Amazon Echo"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 4,
				"Question": "Which AI was invented first?",
				"AnswerOne": "Siri",
				"AnswerTwo": "Alexa",
				"AnswerThree": "Tay",
				"AnswerFour": "Eugene",
				"RightAnswer": "Siri"
			  }	
		]
		},
		{
		"id": 3,
		"questions": 
		[
			  {
				"ID": 1,
				"Question": "What is the best comparison with an AI?",
				"AnswerOne": "It is a killer machine who will steal our jobs",
				"AnswerTwo": "It is a well-equipped toolbox",
				"AnswerThree": "It is just a toy for everyone who is playing video games",
				"AnswerFour": "It is a good replacement for the mankind",
				"RightAnswer": "It is a well-equipped toolbox"
			  },
			  {
				"ID": 2,
				"Question": "Can you save lives “just” with an AI?",
				"AnswerOne": "YES",
				"AnswerTwo": "NO",
				"AnswerThree": "I don't know",
				"AnswerFour": "Maybe",
				"RightAnswer": "NO"
			  },
			  
			  {
				"ID": 3,
				"Question": "What is a specific activity for an AI?",
				"AnswerOne": "Making forecasts and possible courses based on structured data.",
				"AnswerTwo": "To water plants",
				"AnswerThree": "To connect you with the internet and to receive phone calls",
				"AnswerFour": "To transmit network packages",
				"RightAnswer": "Making forecasts and possible courses based on structured data."
			  }	
		]
		}
	]
}